Taiz how are you? Well, one day today I
taiz qué tal estáis bueno yo hoy un día
entered these credits as you know, I wouldn't have
entré a estos créditos como ya sabéis no
checked. I was in the afternoon on
habría comprobado estaba por la tarde en
Juanjo Cadena's live blog. Okay, you
el directo de juanjo cadena blog ok lo
can see it on his channel. Tomorrow I will upload
podéis ver en su canal yo mañana subiré
the best parts or a summary to my
los mejores partes o un resumen a mi
main channel. I was live with
canal principal estaba en directo con
two then immediately connected
dos después inmediatamente empalmado
after that, the members can
después de eso los miembros lo podéis
see it in its entirety. Okay, the members can
ver entero vale los miembros podéis
see it in its entirety both on YouTube and in
verlo entero tanto en youtube como en
tweets on the secondary channel and in
tweets en el canal secundario y en
tweets and nothing. Here we throw potatoes, two or
tweets y nada aquí echamos patatas dos o
three, to the entourage that have emerged today.
tres al séquito que han surgido hoy
Let's see it, let's comment on it. It's about
vamos a verlo vamos a comentarlo es de
having a singer's name. I feel like you're not
tener nombre de cantante siento que no
talking to me x about Carlos Rivera.
me hablas a mí x de a carlos rivera
Thank you very much, thank you very much.
muchísimas gracias muchísimas gracias
Well, to think about, of course, tell you
bueno para pensar por supuesto deciros
that Minister Valeri pointed with the is
que ministra valeri apuntó con los está
blowing up today I have the screen on that you
petando hoy tengo puesta la pantalla que
don't see, forgive me, my kids, period,
no ves perdonarme mis chavalería punto
with the pressing, you know that my
con los apretando ya sabéis que me
kids, period, as it is a website
chavalería punto como es una página web
that has a forum, it has a forum for both
que tiene un foro tiene un foro tanto de
SEO salt and celebrity gossip,
sal seo como de cotilleos de famosos de
reality television, everything you
reality de televisión de todo lo que
want.  and also with
queráis y además con códigos de
discount codes take advantage okay because there is a
descuentos aprovechad vale porque hay
discount code
código de descuento
you have a store
tenéis una tienda
very rich products headphones t-
productos muy ricos auriculares
shirts a collaboration that we have
camisetas una colaboración que tenemos
with the brand racks mafia so take
con la marca racks mafia así que
advantage ok and the mitja valeria dot com
aprovecha ok y la mitja valeria puntocom
and well to rampla with what you can to
y bueno a rampla con lo que podáis a
rampla with what you can if I look
rampla con lo que podáis si tengo cara
tired let's see obviously
de cansado a ver evidentemente
obviously I'm not made of cardboard but here
evidentemente no soy de cartón pero aquí
I am at the foot of the canyon attitude because the
estoy al pie del cañón actitud porque el
salsero does not comment only what has happened
salsero no se comenta sólo que ha pasado
with win michu or and cali to win michu
con win michu or y cali a win michu
well let's see yesterday win michu lass had it I'm going
bueno a ver ayer win michu lass tuvo le
a little she was dealing with it a little
ando un poco la estuvo lidiando un poco
because she shared the statement from my
porque compartió el comunicado de mi
area okay she shared the statement from
área vale compartió el comunicado de
mieres that well I don't know if dallas will have
mieres que bueno no sé si dallas habrá
denied the statement or will have
desmentido el comunicado o habrá
analyzed part of the statement or
analizado por parte del comunicado o
something maybe we will see the video that she
algo a lo mejor vemos el vídeo que ha
uploaded of praise we will see but I
subido de halago ya veremos pero yo
deny my part ok christopher
desmentir la parte mía ok christopher
thank you very much welcome or
muchísimas gracias bienvenida o
welcome welcome but I am mind and
bienvenido bienvenido pero yo es mente y
my part okay because absolutely
la parte mía vale porque absolutamente
no it made no sense to lie
no no tenía sentido faltar a la verdad
javi I always try to see you and today that  it's
javi siempre trato de verte y hoy que es
my birthday it's special to me a
mi cumpleaños es especial para mí un
greeting from you a hug and a greeting to the
saludo de tu parte abrazo y saludo a la
drugs the kids from Argentina something
droga la chavalería desde argentina algo
that not many are around here
que no son muchos por aquí muchísimas
thank you very much thank you
gracias muchísimas gracias leo
very much leo thank you very much congratulations it
muchísimas gracias felicidades que
seems like a great day Hector welcome
parece un gran día héctor bienvenidos
thank you very much the thing is that today in
muchísimas gracias el caso es que hoy en
michu share already outside part of the
michu comparte ya fuera parte del
statement okay and michu share the
comunicado vale y michu comparte el
statement the age and it works to the
comunicado la edad y funciona al
statement with cachondeíto not with
comunicado con cachondeíto no con
cachondeíto immortality for all
cachondeíto inmortalidad para todos
except for the judicial experts
excepto para los peritos judiciales
Francisco Javier Ramírez thank you very much
francisco javier ramírez muchísimas
welcome except for the
gracias bienvenido excepto para los
judicial experts I think they have
peritos judiciales yo creo que se han
come too far with the issue of the expert that
venido muy arriba con el tema del perito
another month that I tell them that all
que otra mes que la las diga que todas
the communities of sal have or have a
las comunidades de sal se o tienen
toxic community except yours and
comunidad tóxica exceptuando la tuya y
that of the da it seems to me a
la de la da me parece un comentario
super super neutral comment it seems to me a
súper súper neutral me parece un
super objective comment things as they
comentario súper objetivo las cosas como
are and I left it like that really it's
son y deje así realmente
been a while since I last passed by the string of the
hace tiempo que no me pasó por el string
fairy for time okay but yes it's
del hada por tiempo vale pero sí que
true that I have a community here
verdad que yo tengo aquí una comunidad
that is my family and that we have a
que soy mi familia y que lo pasamos aquí
great time here and that I don't mind not
estupendamente y que no me importa no
having  50,000 viewers but with those we are with we are doing
tener 50.000 espectadores pero con los
great
que estamos estamos de [__] madre
the brand taste okay well the thing here
la marca gusto vale bueno la cosa aquí
with cachondeíto no I think that they have
con cachondeíto no yo creo que es han
come too far with the issue of the
venido muy arriba con el tema del perito
judicial expert not for nothing no for nothing okay
judicial no por nada no por nada vale
but because now apparently now we will
sino porque ahora por lo visto ahora
see the video of Dallas no the expert
veremos el vídeo de dallas no el perito
the expert has retracted her
la perito se ha retractado de sus
words
palabras
apparently it no longer says that it is not the
por lo visto ya no pone que no sea el
same dog okay she has left it
mismo perro vale lo ha dejado como
open or something like that from what I
abierto o algo así por lo que tengo
understand but well we will see the thing is
entendido pero bueno lo veremos la cosa
no longer the expert herself but the thing is
ya no es la perito en sí sino la cosa es
wait wait until the
espérate espérate a que termine el
process is over because the audience still
proceso porque todavía la audiencia
has to speak
tiene que hablar
Dallas has appealed and the audience has to
dallas ha recurrido y la audiencia tiene
speak okay once they
que hablar vale una vez que te lo
archive it ok then you still
archiven ok pues entonces ya todavía
go out and say hey look what
sales a decir oye mira que esto que me
they reported to me they have archived because they have
denunciaron lo han archivado porque no
seen no evidence and that's it but
han visto indicios y ya está pero de
sniper thank you very much but I think they have
sniper muchas gracias pero yo creo que
come too far and they have spoken
se han venido muy arriba y han hablado
too soon I think he speaks too soon
muy pronto yo creo que habla muy pronto
because look now that in the
porque fíjate tú ahora que en el
statement it has said that if not that it is the
comunicado ha puesto que si no que es la
opportunity for all those who have doubted
oportunidad de todos los que han dudado
her or all those who have thought
de ella o de todos los que han pensado
that she has the dog to
que ella tiene el perro que le pidan
apologize to her or if not she is going to sue them to
disculpas o si no los va a demandar a
laws like let's see if now you are
leyes como a ver si ahora estás venido
very high going to the press and now
muy arriba yendo a la prensa y ahora
the judge or the hearing takes and opens it.
coge la juez o la audiencia y lo abre yo
As far as I understand the hearing
hasta donde tengo entendido la audiencia
I think there are three judges, it is not worth it to me
creo que son tres jueces no me 50 vale
because you are looking at it there on the
porque lo estás mirando por ahí en
internet and I think there are three judges who
internet y creo que son tres jueces que
look at the appeal, look at the evidence that there
miran el recurso miran las pruebas que
is and decide yes to there being a trial, nothing, I
hay y deciden sí a que haya juicio nada
mean, there is no sentence. There are a lot of people out
o sea no hay sentencia hay mucha gente
there because I saw the chips
por ahí porque yo vista los chips
in fact the others that we will talk about later about
de hecho los otros que luego hablaremos
care, almost not very funny, I have seen
de cuido no casi muy gracioso he visto a
the typical ones going around in circles about
los típicos darles vueltas a las cosas
tremendous things, going around in circles to see there is no
tremendas darle vueltas a ver no hay
sentence yet because there has not been a
sentencia todavía porque no ha habido
trial, they have acquitted it,
juicio lo han sobreseído
now Dallas has appealed based on the
ahora dallas ha recurrido en base a las
evidence that he has, what is the
pruebas que él tiene cuáles son las
evidence that he has,
pruebas que tiene me las compensaciones
my compensations that are verified by the
mías que están verificadas por el
court, which I have also seen people
juzgado que también he visto a la gente
going around in circles about that, not the
dándole vueltas a eso no ala
girl, this peace who was a girl that I
chica esta paz que fue una chica que yo
threw out of the account  from twitter because he
le tiré de la cuenta de twitter porque
was insulting me a lot and they
me estaba insultando muchísimo y le
suspended his twitter account because he
suspendieron la cuenta de twitter porque
was insulting me horribly and
me estaba insultando a lo bestia y
then he has another one and he had it
entonces la tiene a otra y me la había
yesterday that suddenly quoted my tweet where
ayer que de repente citó mi tweet donde
I said to leave me alone but if he
yo dije que me dejaran en paz pero si
took my tweet saying how they swallow
tomo mi tweet diciendo cómo se tragan
the lawyers' papers as if they
los papeles de los abogados como si
were court papers Juan thank you very much
fueran papeles del juzgado juan muchas
and it's like no the paper that I
gracias y es como no el papel que yo
showed from the Seville court saying
enseñé del juzgado de sevilla diciendo
that they had verified the good nights
que había verificado los buenas noches
an audio I love your live broadcasts
un audio me encantan tus directos
equally I also love your
igualmente igualmente me encanta tu
honor and Kim thank you very much
honor y kim muchísimas gracias
the paper that I showed from the
el papel que yo enseñé del juzgado de
Seville court saying that they had verified
sevilla diciendo que habían verificado
the conversations [ __ ]
las conversaciones [__]
don't [ __ ] with me be careful and we occur to
no me jodas tener cuidado y nos ocurre
insinuate that it is falsified
insinuar que es falsificado
compensations or anything like that
compensaciones ni nada por el estilo
because they are verified by the court
porque están verificadas por el juzgado
and they are audios
y son audios
most of them are audios apart from what is written
la mayoría son audios aparte que escrita
and part that are audios of that they do not say
y parte que son audios de esa no dicen
anything about the conversations they do not say anything
nada de las conversaciones no dicen nada
here no but well the thing is the
aquí no pero bueno la cosa son las
conversations the photos of the expert report
conversaciones las fotos del peritaje
that the photos are the host not to be the
que las fotos son la [__] no sea la
photo I am not an expert and I cannot
foto yo no soy perito y yo no puedo
rule nothing gamer thank you very much
dictaminar nada gamer muchas gracias
but the photos are the best
pero las fotos son la [__]
the photos are the best there was one there was
las fotos son la [__] había una
one that isn't this one there was one that was this one that is
había una que no es ésta había una que
tremendous
era esta que esta es tremenda
this is tremendous obviously it has
esta es tremenda evidentemente tiene
faces it has faces very good night
cáritas tiene cáritas muy buenas noches
Javi today I am here because I got a
javi hoy estoy aquí porque he conseguido
job and since I am in
curro y como estoy
good shape a little more than other days
bueno un poquito más que otros días
for 2000 now with affection now just in
para el 2000 ahora lo con cariño ahora
case but anyway
lo por si acaso pero bueno muchísimas
thank you very much I am very happy for you these
gracias alegro muchísimo por ti estas
photos are tremendous let's see I am not an expert I am
fotos tremendas a ver yo no soy perito
not going to sign anything okay I have my
yo no voy a firmar nada vale yo tengo mi
opinion based on my conversations
opinión en base a las conversaciones
okay already everything that we are seeing
mías vale ya todo lo que estamos viendo
but this photo is tremendous I mean
pero esta foto es que es tremenda o sea
the two moles that we see here are
los dos lunares que aquí los vemos más
bigger it is older it has gray hair
grandes está más viejito tiene canas
you have faces now from all the years that have
tienes caritas ya de los años que han
passed but this part this part is that it is
pasado pero esta parte esta parte es que
the support
es la apoya
this part is that it is the buoy
esta parte es que es la boya
this here is that it is the best and studies it
esto aquí es que es la [__] y estudios
is good serious for people will have their
es bueno grave por la gente tendrá su
opinion based on these photos damn what are you
opinión en base a estas fotos [__] que
going to tell people it is not like that
le vas a decir a la gente no es así
yet the dog was not a single color
todavía el perro fuera de un único color
okay
vale
the dog is all black or the
el perro es negro entero o el perro
whole white dog well people are still
blanco entero pues la gente todavía se
waiting no but for people to put the
espera no pero para la gente meta la
photo and what they think and then outside of it
foto y que piensan y luego fuera parte
also have a photograph that I will take they
también tienen una fotografía que me
had to urge the archived in which the
tenían instará al archivado en la que al
dog's eyes look more yellow the
perro se le ven los ojos más amarillo la
girlfriend is today you look great very handsome
churri está hoy te ves genial muy guapo
thanks yelled how are you a
gracias gritó qué tal está un abrazo
huge hug well in total I think he speaks
enorme bueno total que yo creo que habla
very soon because based on all these
muy pronto porque en base a todas estas
things it is quite likely I think I think it
cosas es bastante probable yo creo yo
is quite quite likely
creo que es bastante bastante probable
that at least there will be a trial that at
que por lo menos haya juicio que por lo
least the court will open the case
menos la audiencia abra el caso
listen that maybe it opens it and
oye que a lo mejor lo abre y las
acquits them listen very well then you go
absuelve oye pues muy bien entonces es
out and talk okay but I think it
salís y habláis vale pero yo creo que
came out too soon and the press to spawn
salió muy pronto y a la prensa a desovar
faces what happens because things can still
caras que pasa porque todavía puede
change a lot okay but well to
cambiar mucho la cosa vale pero bueno a
my shirt photos I think it is incredible it has
mi camisa fotos me parece increíble está
especially shocked me I had not
sobre todo me ha impactado yo no la
seen it and this is going to impact this
había visto y esta va a impactar esta
part of here project and that guy is aunt
parte de aquí proyecto y ese tío es tía
how the [ __ ] there are two dogs that are so
como [__] hay dos perros que son tan
identical I was not surprised with the
idénticos no me quedé sorprendido con el
video I just saw it now we
vídeo justo lo acabo de ver ahora lo
see it now we see it and that
vemos ahora lo vemos nosotros y eso
well I said that I'm not going to talk  of the subject
bueno he dicho que ni va hablar del tema
but well in this case this video is
pero bueno en este caso este vídeo
quite viral and I speak we see and we do not
bastante viral y hablo vemos y ya no
say anything else that does not say what
decimos más nada que no diga lo que diga
the audience says once they say what
la audiencia una vez que diga lo que
the audience says we have to
diga la audiencia lo tenemos que
respect it we have to respect it okay
respetar lo tenemos que respetar vale
but the fact is that now apparently
pero el caso es que ahora por lo visto
the expert's report has been rectified by the expert
el peritaje lo ha rectificado la perito
and I believe that the expert report I believe
y yo creo que el peritaje yo creo que
was the main thing that gave rise to the
fue lo principal que daba base al
filing of the case but I do not know I do not
archivo de la causa pero no lo sé no lo
know I speak from my opinion always
sé yo hablo desde mi opinión siempre
okay guys total he makes fun he makes
vale chavales total que se burla se
fun of win said here he makes fun and then he
burla win dicho aquí se burla y entonces
comes from Dallas and answers him he still has
viene de dallas y le responde aún tiene
traumas Dallas won't let me live he is
traumas dallas no me deja vivir me está
harassing me from what you see here they have each other
acosando por lo que ve aquí se tienen
unblocked right now it's not like win
desbloqueado ahora mismo no es como win
michu if you don't want mana with Dallas if
michu si no quieres maná con dallas si
in the video you made the other time
en el vídeo que hiciste la otra vez
you said that they should leave you so that they can let you
dijiste que te dejen para que te deje
live in peace that you want to live with
vivir tranquilo que quieres vivir con
your pets and I don't know what what is
tus mascotas y no sé qué a qué viene
this about what is this attack about thank goodness you
esto a qué viene este ataque menos mal
are now just a shadow of a
que ya eres sólo una sombra de un chiste
very bad joke nobody cares except to
muy malo a nadie le importa más que para
repeat the phrase
repetir te la frase
of gray that you yourself said okay  give him
de gris que tú mismo dijiste vale darle
this video
le pone este vídeo
a hammock answers him with photos of this
una hamaca le contesta con fotos de este
actor gives him the video of the
actor le da la le pone el vídeo del
supposed testimony of the supposed
supuesto testimonio de la supuesta
victim of Winston that in theory of
víctima de winston que en teoría de
Sofia and sentence in theory I don't know
sofía y sentencia en teoría no lo sé
I don't have it nexo lexus nexus nexus
yo no la tengo nexo lexus nexus
thank you very much nexus what a
nexus muchísimas gracias nexus vaya
shot we are already on the way to 500 her
sacada estamos ya camino de los 500 sus
eyes air eye good total that today a lot
ojos aire ojo bueno total que hoy mucho
just happy with a photo
sólo contenta con foto
dallas here for a video I'm
dallas aquí le por un vídeo
not scared
no me da miedo
and he answers him again with a baby it
y le vuelve a contestar con un bebé me
seems to me a discussion enough to me the
parece una discusión bastante me la
diffusion enough it seems to me that today
difusión bastante me me parece que hoy
Michel should not get into messing with
míchel no debería entrar en meterse con
Dallas after what he has said like that if he
dallas después de lo que ha dicho así si
has taken it and has said that they do not want anything
ha cogido y ha dicho que no quieren nada
the subject that he does not want controversy to
el tema que no quiere polémica que
solve the thing that he is doing and
solucionar la cosa que está haciendo y
besides I have already seen it two or three
aparte ya lo he visto dos o tres
times
ocasiones
for example in the relief lines a
por ejemplo en los lines de alivio un me
like I go here I can't see it nexus
gusta voy aquí no lo puedo ver nexo
thank you very much I'm going to see if the
muchísimas gracias voy a ver si el
kitten has it around here shared no no no he does not
gatito lo tiene por aquí compartido no
have it he believes it is from what was seen
no no no lo tiene se cree es de lo visto
what was seen they believe he
lo visto se creen
gave him a like day 11
le dio un me gusta día 11
etc
etc
look high  and that he gave her a like on twitter, he's
mirar alto y que le dio like en twitter
very encouraged, so it's not bad
mucho ánimo tiene o sea que no está mal
that he gives her the suite, that they support her friend, she's
que le dé la suite que apoyen a su amiga
not lucky to have found
no tiene suerte de haber dado con
you because if she finds me, I'm not
vosotros porque si da conmigo este yo no
going to court, this can only be fixed by
voy al juzgado esto sólo se arregla
hitting her over the head with a brick, there's
dándole un ladrillazo en la cabeza
no more justice than that
no hay más justicia que esa
michu has given her, what she's done, I do
michu le ha dado le haya hecho
n't know if she'll still maintain it, she'll have
no sé si lo seguirá manteniendo lo habrá
removed it but now she sends a lot of people by
quitado pero ahora manda mucha gente por
email, okay, it's incredible, well, the
email vale es increíble bueno la cosa la
thing is, well, we also have this
cosa es que bueno tenemos también este
other tweet, no, this other tweet from the cat,
otro tweet no este otro tweet del gato
no, where she shares this comment on
no donde comparte este comentario en
instagram in which win michu says that,
instagram en el que win michu dice que
very well, a couple
pues muy bien ya le han llegado un par
of them have already arrived, meaning that she has reported and she
de ella o sea que ha denunciado y mucho
has reported people a lot, she says, no, well,
ha denunciado a gente dice no pues ya
a couple of them have already arrived and it seems that they are
han llegado un par de ellas y parece que
moving forward, several youtubers who
tiran para adelante varios youtubers que
have defamed me are going to have to
me han difamado van a tener que prestar
testify because of the things they have said
declaración por las cosas que han dicho
about me, thanks for asking, okay, and then
de mí gracias por preguntar vale y luego
here they respond with another one that I don't know if it's real, they did
aquí responden con otro que no sé si es
n't check it, I don't know if it's real,
real no lo comprobaban no sé si es real
that you have a normal piece of [ __ ], so if it's
que tengáis un normal de [__] entonces
real, I don't know if it's new, not old,
si es real no sé si nuevo no sea antiguo
but well, it seems to me  curious luis jofré
pero bueno me parece curioso luis jofré
this is a mix and i think he is making a
este es un mix y yo creo que se está
mistake i think that at the time of
equivocando yo creo que a la hora de
having gotten into the mess that he has
haberse metido en el berenjenal que se
gotten into with the people that have gotten into
ha metido con la gente que se ha metido
with the people that are rolling now he
con la gente que se está rodando ahora
is making a mistake because he is
se está equivocando porque está
losing apart from credibility and
perdiendo a parte de credibilidad y
support that let's remember that in 2017 he had a
apoyo que recordemos que en 2017 tenía
lot he is losing a bit of
mucho está perdiendo un poco
forms that do not seem right to me at all if he wants to
formas no me parecen para nada si quiere
show that he has changed it does not seem right to me
demostrar que ha cambiado no me parece
in the way it does not seem right to me in the way of
en la forma no me parece en la forma de
showing that the change has not and that now he is
demostrar que el cambio no y que ahora
going to tell another one of u2 see that you are
te vaya a decirle a otro de u2 ver que
going to denounce them when when you
los vas a denunciar cuando cuando
have always laughed at the complaints
siempre os habéis reído de las denuncias
that dallas makes no and now you go to
que pone dallas no y ahora tú vayas a
sue someone who has criticized you
demandar a alguien que te haya criticado
but denounce someone who has
pero denunciarlo alguien que te haya
criticized you and now that you are going to spend 3 4
criticado y ahora que te vas a pegar 3 4
or 5 years denouncing someone all that
o 5 años denunciando a alguien todo
nonsense so that later I do not know the truth it
rollo ese para que luego no sé la verdad
seems a little desperate what a little
lo ve un poco desesperante lo de un poco
desperate and the thing is that they think
desesperante y la cosa es que se creen
take and put the next tweet okay brow
coge y pone el siguiente tuit vale brow
euro liked
euro le dio like a las condolencias de
dallas' condolences for two cats sadly
dallas por dos gatos tristemente ha
in the end don gato passed away as you all
fallecido al final don gato como todos
know
sabéis
and to give the husband a comment he put
y darle al esposo un comentario le puso
a tweet
un tweet
giving his condolences and so on and according to what they say you
dándole su pésame y demás y según dicen
learn well now he gave him light
se aprende pues ahora le dio light
instead win michu didn't even
en cambio win michu ni siquiera le
write him anything good you know why yes
escribió nada bueno saben porque sí
euronews they have been getting along badly for a while so they don't even
euronews se llevan mal hace rato
write to each other to
entonces ya ni se escriben para
cover it up fact let's see and another one from here they
disimular hecho a ver y otro de aquí se
think he has been emboldened on the one hand
creen es ha envalentonado por una parte
valencianes has been emboldened by the
valencianes ha envalentonado por el
fact that you don't know if win michu
hecho de que tú no sabes si win michu le
has been able to write to him privately euro
ha podido escribir por privada euro yo
for example I
por ejemplo
think I put a tweet or two
creo que puse un tweet o dos
encouragement to see if don gato comes forward I leave I
animo a ver si don gato sale pa lante
said no but I was part of it the whole
salgo puse no pero yo fuera parte todo
time he was asking the room and
el tiempo estaba preguntando la sala y
now privately and then you know
ahora por privado y entonces tú lo sabes
and so I go michu privately that I
y así voy michu por privado que yo
understand that no matter how distant they
entiendo que por muy distanciados que
are I don't know that they had a bad
esté a no sé que hayan tenido un mal
vibe
rollo
something as painful as his cat his
una cosa tan dolorosa como su gato su
pet no I assume that something
mascota no yo doy por hecho que algo por
privately he will have said labrador weighs less
privado habrá dicho labrador pesa menos
and the fact is that he has made a mistake okay
y es que de hecho se ha equivocado vale
because look at her and you will be  very
porque mirar para ella y estarás
saturated and he'll want to rest hoops it's that he did
saturadísimo y él querrá descansar aros
say well a lot of something but
es que sí que dijo buen mucho algo pero
love to Raul
cariño a raúl
although well obviously everyone
aunque bueno obviamente todo el mundo
is there for her and you'll be very
está ahí para ella y estarás
saturated and he'll want to rest but she's
saturadísimo y querrá descansar pero es
a [ __ ] and
una [__]
give your love to Raul
y darle vuestro cariño a raúl
in his live so he told her yes he
en su directo así que le dijo sí que
said something but as I say anyway it
dijo algo pero ya digo igualmente me
seems to me that the
parece muy desproporcionada la
answer that he put on the web michu is very disproportionate
contestación que la metió en web michu
believe me to begin with is that he doesn't
hace créeme para empezar es que no le
mention me what surprises me the most
menciona a mí lo que más me sorprende
this his friend already gave it to me and he kicked me out
esto ya me lo dio su amigo y me echó
when he came to mess with me on twitter
cuando vino a meterse conmigo en twitter
no that if rat that if I don't know that I don't know
no que si rata que si no sé que no sé
how much I enjoy them that he did to me that by the
cuánto los disfruto que me hizo que por
way they were going I saw you it's something that just
cierto iban te vi es una cosa que se me
came to my head
acaba de venir a la cabeza
in a moment of peace maybe or rather I
en su momento de paz igual o sea que yo
put a tweet where she didn't mention it okay
puse un tuit donde no lo mencionaba vale
dude it's secret net she's a youtuber with 30
tío es secret net es una youtuber de 30
thousand subscribers I don't know how many
mil suscriptores no sé cuántos
followers she has on twitter guys I mean she
seguidores tiene en twitter tíos o sea
has she thinks she's on twitter
que tiene se cree ente en twitter
youtube little 3000 of three thousand
youtube pequeñita 3000 de tres mil
subscribers if you come to  twitter
suscriptores si vienes al twitter de
how do you find out about this tweet how do you
cómo te enteras de este tweet cómo te
find out about this tweet is that I get
enteras de este tweet es que a mí me da
the feeling I need to be closer or not
la sensación necesitaré acercado o no
but I get the feeling many times
pero a mí me da sensación muchas veces
that they are in a tortilla group waiting
que están en un grupo tortilla pendiente
for what we say what we don't say they
de lo que decimos lo que no decimos se
pass it on if not only does it happen you put this I
lo pasan si no sólo pasa tu ponga esto
put this you for the other if not
yo pongo esto tú por lo otro si no te
mention yourself that it doesn't even say good
menciones que ni siquiera pone buen
saying because he put the w
dicho porque ha puesto la w
how the [ __ ] does good michu appear in the
como [__] aparece buen michu en el
tweet of this girl that I already tell you that she
tuit de esta chavala que ya os digo que
has made a mistake she grows because they go you
se ha equivocado se crece porque van
think it's not
pensáis que no
here she puts [ __ ] just to put wool
es aquí mete [__] por meter lana
because you don't know what they can
porque tú no sabes lo que ellos puedes
say in private that yes that I
decir por privado que sí que yo
evidently believe that there will be a play
evidentemente creo que habrá un play
with michu today they are like no like that
with michu a día de hoy están de no
we put michu why the [ __ ] here
así ponemos michu para qué [__] por aquí
the w
la w
is true here I go by bike or in other words
es verdad por aquí voy en bici o sea que
here the w for what does it put the w for what does it put
por aquí la w para que pone la w para
the w but well let's see I do
que pone la w pero bueno a ver yo sí
think that I go michu lauro is more
pienso que voy michu lauro está más
distant today I have my reasons
distanciada día de hoy tengo mis bases
to think the same type okay but from
para pensar el mismo tipo vale pero de
there to not giving weight to putting
ahí a que no le haya dar peso a poner
half say win  my turn puts nothing, I
medio decir win mi turno le pone nada o
mean, to begin with, she said it
sea para empezar es que lo ha dicho en
live and to finish, although I haven't
un directo y para terminar aunque no lo
said it in public at least they have been
he dicho en público a lo menos se han
done privately, you can't take
hecho por privado no puede dar por hecho
things you don't know for granted, but the response is
cosas que no sabe pero la respuesta es
disproportionate, disproportionate, look how
desproporcionada desproporcionada mira
miserable you are, taking
que eres miserable
advantage of the death of an animal to
aprovechar la muerte de un animal para
create salsa and post a tweet like this,
crear salsa y poner un tweet como este
but well, it doesn't surprise me, coming from
pero bueno no me sorprende viniendo de
you, the response seems very disproportionate to me, it
ti me parece muy desproporcionada la
seems to me to be proof that a
respuesta me parece muestra de que un
myth already has it between the eyebrows, that she
mito ya la tiene entre ceja y ceja de
already has it fixed, that she hasn't
que ya la tiene fijada de que no la
seen it, no, it doesn't sound familiar to me, she
tiene vista no no me suena
seems like a very prudent youtuber, she
me parece una youtuber muy prudente se
thinks she doesn't sound familiar to me, at some point, let's see, she disrespects me, I'm
cree no me suena en algún momento a ver
going michu, correct me
le falta el respeto voy michu corregirme
if I'm wrong, okay, so that you have it
si me equivoco vale para que la tengas
without so so so signed ballet and they have
sin tan tan tan fichada ballet y tienen
like signed who are the youtubers
como fichados quienes son los youtubers
that support her at all, I don't know what she
que que le apoya nada lado no sé qué
knows and I find it very curious, she tells her to
sabe y me resulta muy curioso le diga
take advantage of the death of an animal to
aprovechar la muerte de un animal para
create salsa today michu this that churri
crear salsa hoy michu esto que churri
as well here more your genes and this
como bien aquí más vuestra genes y esto
that churri
que churri
this what churri that this tweet look at you
esto qué churri que este tuit fíjate tú
no he talks about the death of his cat and
no el habla de la muerte de su gato y lo
relates it to this tweet from dallas this
relaciona con este tweet de dallas este
tweet I think is not a response to this one this one is
tuit yo creo que no es respuesta a este
put here but if you
este lo ponen aquí pero si os dais
notice to start with to start look at
cuenta para empezar para empezar mirad
the color of the font here in the lines
el color de la fuente aquí en los lines
and here in red okay apart different you
y aquí en rojo vale aparte diferente
are like more bold and it is
estás como más negritas y está más
clearer or rather it is not a
clarita o sea no es no es una captura de
full screenshot they are two
pantalla completa son dos capturas de
screenshots joined together okay they are two
pantallas unidas vale son dos capturas
screenshots joined together okay these
de pantallas unidas vale estas capturas
screenshots were passed to me separately by
de pantalla me la pasaron por separado a
certain people on one occasion when
mí ciertas personas en una ocasión que
I was going to be a video against dallas
yo iba a ser un vídeo contra dallas hace
many years ago okay they passed them to me
muchos años vale me la pasaron por
separately as if they were related
separado como si estuvieran relacionadas
then with time I found out that it
luego con el tiempo me enteré que no
was not related that this tweet from
estaba relacionado que este tweet de
dallas had nothing to do with this tweet
dallas no tenía que ver con este tweet
from win michu
de win michu
okay
vale
for me w's response is fine since
para mí la respuesta de w está bien
that attack is in bad taste it's
puesto que ese ataque es de mal gusto
normal that he answers like that the attack is in
normal que le conteste así el ataque de
bad taste but the response is also
mal gusto pero la respuesta también
the attack is in bad taste but the response is
el ataque de mal gusto pero la respuesta
also in the end in the end
también es al final al final
I think he went too far with the
yo creo que se ha pasado más con la
response than with other things I think it would have been
respuesta que con otras cosas yo creo
smarter instead
que hubiera sido más inteligente en vez
of having  since the fact of using the
de haber puesto el hecho de utilizar la
death of an animal, when we can get
muerte de un animal no cuando te podemos
this out of you, I think it would have been more
sacar esto yo creo que hubiera sido más
appropriate to have put it, your
adecuado que lo hubiera puesto tu
little mouth stays there and you'll be
boquita se quede ahí y estarás
completely saturated and they're going to rest it, but
saturadísimo y lo van a descansar pero
it's for your little mouth, it's believed in it, with
es para tu boquita se cree en ella con
that it would have been [ __ ] great, it would have been [ __ ] great, it would have been [ __ ]
eso hubiera quedado de [__] madre
great. Well, the
hubiera quedado de [__] madre bueno la
thing, the thing, the thing
cosa la cosa la cosa la cosa
is that in this tweet, okay, they put the
es que en este tuit vale que ponen aquí
two related ones here, we see that win michu,
los dos relacionados vemos que win michu
this tweet is from July 2, 2014 at
este tweet es del 2 de julio del 2014 a
7:30
las 7 y media
at 7:30 and here
a las siete y media y aquí
the date is cut off, it doesn't fit on the screen, the screen does
se corta la fecha no cabe en la pantalla
n't fit, okay, but
no cabe la pantalla vale pero sin
nevertheless, here we have the full tweet,
embargo aquí tenemos el tuit completo
this tweet is
este tuit es anterior
prior to this study,
este estudio anterior a este por lo
prior to this one, therefore, therefore, this tweet to which Antonia gives light, okay, or thanks her, gorgeous, look at my daughter, how she looks at my daughter giving me a line, her father, thank you for everything, I look at you eating pasta in sauce with mozzarella cheese, my
pasta en salsa con quesito mozarella mi
favorite,
favorito
a huge hug, then back,
un abrazo enorme entonces de vuelta
capture according to the structure, Antonio
captura según la estructura antonio le
gives you a like, Antonio in this  moment
da like a tui antonio en este momento
antonio approves this tweet right now
antonio aprueba este tuit
antonia approves this
en este momento antonia aprueba este
tweet ok wing michu you are using
tuit ok wing michu estás utilizando
a tweet that has nothing to do
encima un tuit que no tiene nada que ver
with the other one you relate it to invent
con el otro lo relaciona para inventarse
that he is attacking you and you are
que te está atacando a ti y estás
making a jump or taking advantage of the fact
haciendo salcé o aprovechando el hecho
man wing michu
hombre wing michu
anyway
en fin
life goes on and wim and continues being
la vida continúa y wim y continúa siendo
wind michu what are we going to do
wind michu que le vamos a hacer